Ned Schnurman Video Collection
Ned Schnurman Video Collection
- Video
  - Workers '80 (Part I) (Inter America Productions) 01/01/1980 [schnur_100], (Umatic) (Box 6)
  - Workers '80 (Part II) (Inter America Productions) 01/01/1980 [schnur_101], (Umatic) (Box 7)
  - World Gathering: The Final Day (1 of 2) (WNET/PBS) 06/18/1981 [schnur_132], (Umatic) (Box 8)
  - World Gathering: The Final Day (2 of 2) (WNET/PBS) 06/18/1981 [schnur_133], (Umatic) (Box 8)
  - World: The Clouded Window (Second Season Version) (WGBH) 04/03/1979 [schnur_171], (Umatic) (Box 11)
  - WW II clip reel [schnur_213], (VHS) (Box 13)
  - WWII clip reel (Monitor) [schnur_114], (Umatic) (Box 7)
  - WWII clip reel: London Burns, Reporters in London circa WWII, Cronkite [schnur_097], (Umatic) (Box 6)
  - WWII clips reel: D-Day, Submarines-Pacific, Gazela, Lucien Aigner [schnur_183], (Umatic) (Box 12)
  - WWII Footage ("Casablanca Airport") [schnur_137], (Umatic) (Box 9)
  - WWII Footage ("Casablanca Preview") [schnur_214], (Umatic) (Box 13)
  - WWII Footage ("Casablanca Preview") 08/11/1992 [schnur_215], (Umatic) (Box 13)